Guide to the Rick Lazio Papers, 1981–2005
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Congressional Papers
  - Campaign Files
    - Reference File – Hispanics, (Lazio Press Clippings, Memoranda), Sep 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – Housing, (Memoranda, Press Clippings), 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – Lazio Press Releases, Mar-Jul 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – NEA, (Correspondence), Feb-Jul 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – Seniors, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Aug-Sep 1995 (Box 38)
    - Survey Responses By R. Lazio, (New York Times, Project Vote Smart, Suffolk Life, Sierra Club), Apr-Oct 1996; (2 folders) (Boxes 38, 157)
    - Television Spots, Draft Text, Budgets, Shot Lists, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 38)
    - Thank You Letters To Rick Lazio, Dec 1995-Jul 1996 (Box 38)
    - Advertisement Copy, (Includes Sample of Lazio For Congress "Baseball/Trading Card" (water damaged), 1998 (Box 38)
    - Board of Elections, (Signed Acceptance Form For Nomination For Election To The Public Office of ‘Representative In Congress’), 27 May 1998 (Box 38)
    - Candidate Designating Petitions, (Suffolk Co. Republican Committee Designating Convention Agenda), May-Jul 1998 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence, (Letters of Congratulations), Oct-Nov 1998 (Box 38)
    - Debate Prep File, (Opening/Closing Points, Memoranda, Major Points Covered, Notes, Campaign Message Summary, Talking Points On Managed Care, Education, Arts, Social Security, Taxes, Opposition Profiles, Candidate Questionnaire), 1998; (3 folders) (Box 38)
    - Election Analysis Memoranda, (Includes Recommendations For Campaign Speeches/Talking Points), Jan-Nov 1998 (Box 38)
    - Election Night Celebration Logistics, (Memoranda), Nov 1998 (Box 38)
    - Endorsement Letters, Aug-Oct 1998 (Box 38)
    - Endorsement Letters, Sep-Oct 1998 (Box 39)
    - Heritage Foundation, (Essay by Steve Forbes), Oct 1997 (Box 39)
    - House Republican Conference, (Resource Kits, Issue Briefs), Jun-Oct 1998 (Box 39)
    - Labor Issues, (AFL-CIO Correspondence, Endorsement), Jun-Aug 1998 (Box 39)
    - League of Conservation Voters, (Lazio National Environmental Score Card, Lazio Environmental Accomplishments), 1998 (Box 39)
    - Long Island Election District Targets, (Lists, Map of 2nd District), 1998 (Box 39)
    - Long Island Newspaper Ads, (Check Request, Invoices, Adverts), 1998 (Box 39)
    - Long Island Supermarket Canvassing Maps, 1998 (Box 39)
    - Memo RE: R. Giuliani, NY State GOP, Senate Race, 9 Nov 1998 (Box 39)
    - National Association of Retired Federal Employees, (Correspondence), Jun-Oct 1998 (Box 39)
    - Opinion Poll, Aug 1998; (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - Phone Survey Text, Republican National Committee Phone Banks Training Booklet, 1998 (Box 40)
    - Project Vote Smart, (1998 Congressional Political Awareness Test) (Box 40)
    - Registered Voters List, Long Island, (Includes CD of Voter Files), 1998 (Box 40)
    - Republican Assembly Campaign Committee, (Correspondence Supporting John Faso), Sep 1998 (Box 40)
    - Republican Party Analysis, (Memo/Briefing RE: National Trends, R.N.C. Statements, Talking Points), Jan 1998 (Box 40)
    - Sierra Club, (Correspondence, Endorsement Letter…1 Aug 1996, Press Clippings), Mar 1996-Oct 1998 (Box 40)
    - Television and Direct Mail, Check Requests, Budgets, Sep-Oct 1998 (Box 40)
    - Volunteer and Grassroots Campaign Strategy, (Canvassing and Volunteer Information), 1998 (Box 40)
    - Web Site Text, Oct 1998 (Box 40)
    - Wirthlin Worldwide Training, Brand Strategy For The Republican Party, (Power Point Printouts, Voter Decision Making Model, Communication Training/Strategy, Lazio Presentation Text, Speech Samples, Memoranda on Training/Speech Modules, Handwritten Notes), Aug 1998; (3 folders) (Box 40)
    - VIP List – CONFIDENTIAL, 1998 (Box 162)
    - Correspondence, E-Mail, Staff Correspondence Regarding Poll Results, Lazio Voting Record, May-Jul 1999 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, (Thank You Letters), Jan 2000 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence
    - Congratulatory, Nov 1992 (Box 41)
    - Thank You Letters From Rick Lazio, Nov-Dec 1992; (3 folders) (Box 41)
    - Clinton, Bill, Jun 1993 - Aug 2000 (Box 41)
    - Personal, Holiday Cards (Lazio Family), 1993-2002 (Box 41)
    - Congressional Races – Requesting Lazio Support, Feb-Jun 1994 (Box 41)
    - Thank You Card From CNN, (Producers of "Crossfire" To R. Lazio, 1996 (Box 41)
    - Israel – Middle East – Letters To Rick Lazio, (Includes Letter From White House Asst. To Pres. For National Security Affairs 4/29/97), Apr 1997-Mar 1999 (Box 41)
    - Israel/Middle East – White House, (Correspondence To Rick Lazio), Mar 1997-Apr 1998 (Box 41)
    - Al Ghadi, Omer – Congressional Letter Requesting Award Payment, (Includes Return Letter From Dept. of State 1/5/1999), 1998 (Box 41)
    - Birthday Notes, Mar 1998 (Box 41)
    - Congratulatory Letters, Re-Election, Nov 1998-Jan 1999; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Holocaust Issues, (Letters To R. Lazio RE: Holocaust Victims, Nazi Gold, Art Museum Directors Task Force…Includes Letter From Dir. Of National Gallery of Art 2/13/1998), Feb 1998-Oct 1999 (Box 41)
    - Thank You Letters From Members of Congress, Jan 1998-Dec 2000; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Thank You Letters From R. Lazio, Apr-Nov 1998; (3 folders) (Box 42)
    - Thank You Letters, (Re-election Correspondence from R. Lazio), Jan-Dec 1998; (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Thank You Letters, Letters of Support To R. Lazio, Jan-Dec 1998; (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Thank You Letters To Rick Lazio For His Legislative Support/Voting Record, Mar-Oct 1998 (Box 43)
    - Constituent Requests, Feb 1999 (Box 43)
    - ‘Dear Colleague’ Letters From Rick Lazio, Jan 1999-Nov 1999; (2 folders) (Boxes 43, 157)
    - Gingrich, Newt, (Letter Appointing Rick Lazio To Presidential Advisory Commission On Holocaust Assets), 1 Jan 1999 (Box 43)
    - Letters (Form Letters) From Rick Lazio Responding To Constituents Regarding Misc. Issues, 1999; (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Letters of Support and Thanks From Members of Congress, Jan-Dec 1999; (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Personal Correspondence, (Birthday Letters), Mar 1999 (Box 43)
    - Thank You Letters From D.C. Reps and Associations, Jan-Dec 1999; (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Thank You Letters From N.Y. State Officials, Jan-Dec 1999 (Box 43)
    - Thank You Letters To R. Lazio, Jan-Dec 1999; (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Thank You, Congratulatory, Etc. From R. Lazio, Jan-Nov 1999; (5 folders) (Box 44)
    - Thank You Letters To Rick Lazio, Jan 1999 Apr 2000 (Box 44)
    - Birthday Notes, Mar 2000 (Box 44)
    - Fundraising Letters From Rick Lazio, Jun-Sep 2000 (Box 44)
    - Invitation From Pres. And Mrs. Clinton To Congressional Holiday Ball, 4 Dec 2000 (Box 44)
    - Letters of Condolence, Jun 2000 (Box 44)
    - Thank You, Congratulatory, Etc. From R. Lazio, Jan-Nov 2000; (4 folders) (Box 45)
    - Thank You Letters From Members of Congress, Jan-Dec 2000; (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Thank You Letters From New Yorkers, (Includes Note Card From Tom Brokaw), Jan-Dec 2000 (Box 45)
    - Thank You Letters From Rick Lazio, Dec 2000 (Box 45)
    - Thank You Letters To R. Lazio, Jan-Dec 2000 (Box 45)
    - Thank You Letters To R. Lazio For Legislative Support, Mar-Oct 2000 (Box 45)
  - Event
    - District Events Attended by Lazio Staff, 1993-1998; (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Political Action Committee Fundraiser ‘Taste of Long Island’, (Correspondence, Invitation Sample, Attendance Lists), Mar-Oct 1993 (Box 46)
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Fundraiser, (Correspondence, Background Material), Sep-Oct 1993 (Box 46)
    - Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, Lazio Fundraiser, (Event Invitation, Notes, Mailings Lists, Correspondence), 22 Mar 1994 (Box 46)
    - Bob Dole Event, (Lazio Introduction, Draft Notes, Background Material Regarding Pres Clinton Positions, Correspondence, Copy of Letter to Dole, 9/9/93), 18 Feb 1994 (Box 46)
    - Budget Committee, Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, Lazio Fundraiser, (Event Invitation, Talking Points, Correspondence, Mailing Lists), 21 Sep 1994 (Box 46)
    - Jack Kemp Luncheon, (Event Invitation, Notes, Correspondence), 20 Jun 1994 (Box 46)
    - Misc. Fundraising Events, (Correspondence and Background Material), Mar 1994-Aug 1996 (Box 46)
    - Banking and Financial Services Committee, Lazio Fundraiser, (Event Invite, Correspondence, Mailing Lists), 8 Mar 1995 (Box 46)
    - Banking and Financial Services Committee, Lazio Fundraiser, (Event Invitation, Correspondence, Mailing List), 12 Sep 1995 (Box 46)
    - Capital Hill Club Fundraiser Breakfast, Jan-Apr 1995 (Box 46)
    - Capitol View Forum Breakfast, (Correspondence, Talking Points), 6 Apr 1995 (Box 46)
    - Chicago H.U.D., Subcommittee Hearing, Troubled Public Housing, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Oct 1995 (Box 47)
    - Invitations To Events – Accepted, Jan 1995-Sep 1996; (32 folders) (Boxes 47, 48, 49, 50)
    - Pharmaceutical Luncheon, (Guest List, Issue Summary), Sep 1995 (Box 51)
    - Political Action Committee Fundraising, Aug 1995-Aug 1996; (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - American University Washington College Of Law Centennial Celebration, (Speech Drafts, Centennial Programs), 13 Apr 1996 (Box 51)
    - Irish Ambassador, Dermot A. Gallagher Visit, (Correspondence, Memoranda), 31 May 1996 (Box 51)
    - American Telemarketing Association Breakfast, (Talking Points), 23 Apr 1997 (Box 51)
    - Black History Month, (Film Screening Of Mandela and De Klerk, Deer Park L.I., Correspondence), Feb-Mar 1997 (Box 51)
    - Blooming Grove Senior Housing, (Notes, Correspondence, Background Material), 20 Apr 1997 (Box 51)
    - Cold War/Veteran’s Day, (Speech Drafts, Press Release RE: Lazio Cold War Recognition Bill), Nov 1997 (Box 51)
    - Exhibition, UNA Storia Segreta, (Press Release, Talking Points, Background Information, Correspondence), Aug-Sep 1997 (Box 51)
    - Freedom Alliance/President’s Roundtable, (Correspondence Including Letter From Oliver North (10/16/97), Speech Drafts, Talking Points), 6 Dec 1997; (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Global Climate Change, EEI Breakfast, (Talking Points), 24 Sep 1997 (Box 51)
    - Habitat For Humanity Symposium, (Introduction Text RE: Rick Lazio, Agenda, Correspondence, Habitat For Humanity Newsletters, Pamphlet – ‘The House That Congress Built’), 15 Sep 1997 (Box 51)
    - Habitat For Humanity Symposium, (Press Clippings, Releases, Notes…includes newsletter featuring R. Lazio, "The Houses That Congress Built"), 15 Sep 1997 (Box 51)
    - Independent Insurance Agents of America Downstate Insurance Associations Counsel Conference, (Correspondence, Statement by Dennis Ryan, Related Press Material), 6 Nov 1997 (Box 51)
    - Interview (Newsday) With R. Lazio, (Material Listing Lazio’s Legislative Priorities, "Phrases That Identify Rep. Rick Lazio, Local and National Accomplishments), Jan 1997 (Box 51)
    - LA Grange, Transitional Services of New York For Long Island, (Lazio Speech Drafts, Talking Points, Correspondence, Research Material), 21 Nov 1997 (Box 52)
    - Long Island Savings Bank Breakfast, (Talking Points, Press Clippings, Background Information), Jul 1997 (Box 52)
    - March For Life, (Lazio Office "Sign In" Sheet, (Memoranda), 22 Jan 1997 (Box 52)
    - National Italian-American Foundation Congressional Briefing, (Lazio Talking Points, Notes, Correspondence, Background Material), 24 Oct 1997 (Box 52)
    - New York Housing Forum, AIG Lunch, (Forum Schedule, Correspondence, Participant Background Info), 18 Jun 1997 (Box 52)
    - New York Housing Forum, Albany, NY, (Lazio Remarks, Press Release, Transcript of Discussion, Agenda, Background Material, Correspondence, Notes, Participant Bios), 2 Apr 1997; (5 folders) (Box 52)
    - New York Housing Forum, Boston, MA, (Metropolitan Boston Housing Partnership Agenda, Correspondence, Background Material), 16 Jun 1997 (Box 52)
    - New York Housing Forum, Buffalo, NY, (Lazio Remarks, Schedules, Participant List, Correspondence, Notes, Press Coverage, Background Material, Participant Bios), 14 Jul 1997; (4 folders) (Box 52)
    - New York Housing Forum, Rochester, NY, (Lazio Remarks, Agenda, Participant Lists, Press Release, Transcript of Discussion, Correspondence, Notes, Participant Bios), 27 May 1997; (6 folders) (Box 53)
    - New York Housing Forum, Rochester, NY, (Itinerary, Participant Bios), 27 May 1997 (Box 53)
    - Rep. Mike Forbes TV Show, (Topics Discussed – Budget, Economy, Etc.), 9 Apr 1997 (Box 53)
    - Schenectady County GOP Annual Oktoberfest, (Speech Drafts, with notes, Agenda, Notes, Correspondence, Background Material, Press Clippings), 10 Oct 1997; (3 folders) (Box 53)
    - Suffolk County Drug Treatment Court Graduation, (Lazio Speech, Drafts, Notes, Correspondence, Background Information), 10 Dec 1997 (Box 53)
    - T.V. 55 Interview, (Goldisc Superfund Site, EPA Clean Up, Briefing Material), Feb 1997 (Box 53)
    - Town Meeting Presentation By R. Lazio, (Script and Visuals Used For Projection), 26-28 Aug 1997 (Box 53)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Medal of Honor Press Event, (Talking Points, Notes, Correspondence, Background and Research Material, Formal Argument For The Congressional Medal Award, Submitted By R. Lazio), 27 Oct 1997; (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - "Tuesday Group" Meeting, (Discussion Draft, Legislature Agenda), 16 Apr 1997 (Box 54)
    - United Parcel Service, (Lazio Talking Points), 26 Nov 1997 (Box 54)
    - Women’s National Republican Club, (Lazio Speech/Talking Points, Correspondence, Lazio Press Clips), 27 Oct 1997 (Box 54)
    - Action Long Island Lunch/Trial Lawyers, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Background Material, Notes, Notes, Correspondence, Background Material), 27 Oct 1998; (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Advancement For Commerce and Industry Luncheon, (Agenda, Notes, Correspondence, Background Material), 14 Oct 1998 (Box 54)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees AFL-CIO, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence), 24 Jun 1998 (Box 54)
    - American Legion, Babylon Long Island, (Lazio Talking Points, Correspondence), 30 May 1998 (Box 54)
    - America’s Role In The World Economy – The Bridge Group, (Speech Text, Correspondence, Background Material, Lazio Floor Statement For H.R. 3736), 9 Oct 1998 (Box 54)
    - Banco Popolare Di Milano Meeting, (Memoranda, Press Clippings), Oct 1998 (Box 54)
    - Bay Shore Summit (taping), (Speech Drafts, Correspondence), Feb 1998-Feb 1999 (Box 54)
    - Cablevision Press Conference RE: Television Access To Yankee Baseball, (Talking Points, Correspondence), Oct 1998 (Box 54)
    - Cancer March, (Talking Points, Press Release, Correspondence), Sep 1998 (Box 54)
    - Children’s Cancer, Town Hall Forum, (Talking Points, Lazio Introduction Text, 2 Sep 1998 (Box 54)
    - East Patchogue Alliance Inc,(Background Information), 28 Oct 1998 (Box 54)
    - Equality Houses First Low Income Housing Tax Credit, (Press Conference, Text, Correspondence), 13 Jul 1998 (Box 54)
    - ‘Fire Island News’ Interview, (Drafts of Letter To Editor, Talking Points), Jun-Aug 1998 (Box 55)
    - Foster Grand Parent Program, (Speech Drafts, Background Material), 3 Jun 1998 (Box 55)
    - Giuliani Dinner – Lindenhurst Republican Party Dinner, (Speech Text), 15 Mar 1998 (Box 55)
    - Giuliani, Rudolph – Meeting RE: Housing Issues, Includes Memo RE: NYC Legislative Action, Nov 1998 (Box 55)
    - High-Tech Long Island, (Press Release, Correspondence), Aug 1998 (Box 55)
    - Invitations – Speaking Engagements, (Meetings, Events, Correspondence, Memoranda), May-Sep 1998; (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Italian American War Veterans, (Lazio Talking Points, Remarks), 14 Jun 1998 (Box 55)
    - Long Island Business Development Corp., (Lazio Speech, Talking Points, Background Material), 2 Feb 1998 (Box 55)
    - Memorial Day, American Legion Post 365, (Speech Drafts, Press Releases, Background Material, Renderings of National WWII Memorial, Washington D.C.), 25 May 1998 (Box 55)
    - Nassau and Suffolk County Bar, Elder Law Committee, (Correspondence), 26 Jan 1998 (Box 55)
    - National Emergency Response Team, (Correspondence), 21 Nov 1998 (Box 55)
    - National Italian American Foundation, (Speech Drafts, Notes, Background Material), 24 Jun 1998; (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - National Kidney Association, (Itinerary, Lazio Speech), 17-19 Jul 1998 (Box 55)
    - NY Republican Delegation Meeting, (Correspondence, Washington Update Newsletters, "Federal Priorities" Memo 11/17/1998), Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 55)
    - NYS Delegation Meeting, (Includes Letter From R. Lazio RE: Patient Home Care), 21 May 1998 (Box 55)
    - NY State Society of CPA’s, (Speech Text, Event Information, Correspondence, Background Information, Reference, Collected Speeches, -not by R. Lazio), 18 May 1998; (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Parents of Murdered Children, (Agenda, Talking Points, Correspondence, Notes, Background Material), 26 Apr 1998 (Box 56)
    - POW/MIA Armed Forces Day, (Talking Points, POW-MIA Letter From R. Lazio To Pres. Clinton (5/14/1998), Correspondence, Background Material), 16 May 1998 (Box 56)
    - Real Estate Nightmares Radio Show, (Interview Questions, Correspondence, Press Releases), Jul-Dec 1998 (Box 56)
    - Salute To Women Veterans, (Talking Points, Agenda, Correspondence, Background Material), 14 Nov 1998 (Box 56)
    - Sayville Chamber of Commerce, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Background Material), 11 Aug 1998 (Box 56)
    - Southside Hospital Auxiliary National Volunteer Week, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence), Apr 1998 (Box 56)
    - Speaking Engagements – St. John’s Law School, The Enterprise Foundation, Reach, Etc., (Correspondence, Background Material), Jul 1998 (Box 56)
    - Speaking Engagements – Action Long Island, L.I. Labor Coalition, Low Income Housing, (Correspondence, Background Material), Oct 1998 (Box 56)
    - Speaking Engagements – Misc. Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), May-Aug 1998 (Box 56)
    - Speaking Engagements Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Nov 1998 (Box 56)
    - Speaking Engagements Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Dec 1998 (Box 56)
    - Suffolk County American Legion Mtg., (Talking Points, Correspondence, Background Material), 18 Oct 1998 (Box 57)
    - Suffolk County Young Republicans, (Lazio Speech Draft), 27 Apr 1998 (Box 57)
    - Temple Beth David Brotherhood Meeting, (Talking Points, Correspondence, Background Material), 11 Oct 1998 (Box 57)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Medal of Honor, (Correspondence, Press Releases, Lazio Testimony, Floor Statement…Includes Testimony of Roosevelt Great-Grandson), Sep 1997-Oct 1998; (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - Theodore Roosevelt, Video Tape Interview At Sagamore Hill, L.I., (Video Script, Preparatory Material For Taping), 12 Feb 1998 (Box 57)
    - Veteran’s Day, Calverton National Cemetery, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Background Material), 11 Nov 1998 (Box 57)
    - "View From The Hill" Broadcast, (Tax Reform Debate, Script, Outline), 19 Mar 1998 (Box 57)
    - "View From The Hill", (Material For Broadcast From House Recording Studio, RE: Cancer Research), 7 Jan 1998 (Box 57)
    - Washington College of Law Dinner, Myers Society Dinner, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Background Material), 6 Nov 1998 (Box 57)
    - Washington College of Law, (Speech, Press Clippings, Background Material), 29 Sep 1998 (Box 57)
    - Washington College of Law, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Research/Background Material), 29 Sep 1998; (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - Wirthlin Institute, (Speech Drafts), 1998 (Box 57)
    - American Institute of Certified Accountants Conference, (Correspondence, Fact Sheets, Digest of Washington Issues), 4 May 1999 (Box 57)
    - Association of Towns of The State of New York, (Speech Drafts, Notes, Press Clippings), 18 Feb 1999 (Box 57)
    - Breast and Cervical Cancer Treatment Act Press Conference, (Press Releases, Talking Points, Background Material), 22 Mar 1999 (Box 57)
    - Cancer Clinical Trials Amendment Press Conference, (Lazio Talking Points, Press Releases, Correspondence), 14 Sep 1999 (Box 58)
    - Columbia County Republican Party Lincoln Day Dinner, (Speech Drafts, Notes, Background Material), 18 Feb 1999 (Box 58)
    - Congressional Swearing-In Event Details, (Correspondence RE: 106th Congressional Ceremony…Includes Letter From R. Lazio To Justice Antonin Scalia 12/28/1998), 1999 (Box 58)
    - Consulting Engineers Council of NY State Spring Conference, (Speech Text), 6 Jun 1999 (Box 58)
    - D-Day, Long Island Vets Awards Ceremony, (Press Release, Program, Correspondence), 13 Jun 1999 (Box 58)
    - Italian Americans Civil Liberties Act Press Conference, (Talking Points Include Discussion of Race Against Hillary Clinton, Press Releases, Correspondence), 1 Jul 1999 (Box 58)
    - Jeremy and Julia’s Law/The Children’s Place, Albany, NY, (Press Releases, Talking Points, Lazio Statement, Background Material), 1999 (Box 58)
    - NYS GOP Delegation Meeting, (Correspondence, Notes, Mtg. Agenda), 19 Jan 1999 (Box 58)
    - National Audubon Society of New York, (Press Releases, Correspondence), 2 Oct 1999 (Box 58)
    - National Italian American Foundation, (Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Background Material), 25 Jan 1999 (Box 58)
    - National Italian American Foundation, (Speech, Correspondence), 16 Oct 1999 (Box 58)
    - Panama Week, (Schedule, Correspondence), Aug-Oct 1999 (Box 58)
    - RNC Eagles Upstate Stump Speech, (Notes and Speech Text, Includes Lazio Statement On Impeachment, Nomination For J.C. Watts), 12 Jan 1999 (Box 58)
    - Southside Hospital Seasonal Ball, (Drafts of Lazio Statement As Honorary Chairman), Apr 1999 (Box 58)
    - Southwest Airlines Opens Service To Long Island MacArthur Airport, (Talking Points, Background Material), 15 Mar 1999 (Box 58)
    - Speaking Engagements – Italian American Foundation, American Electronics Association, L.I. Builders Association, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jan 1999 (Box 58)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Feb 1999 (Box 58)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Apr 1999 (Box 58)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), May 1999; (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Jun 1999; (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence), Jul 1999; (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence), Aug 1999 (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Sep 1999 (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Oct 1999; (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Nov 1999 (Box 59)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Dec 1999 (Box 60)
    - "Talking Taxes Around The Kitchen Table", (Including Copy of Letter From L.I. Constituent Inviting R. Lazio To Tea), 8 Mar 1999 (Box 60)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors, Washington D.C., (Correspondence, Agenda), 26-29 Jan 1999 (Box 60)
    - Univ. of Washington, (Speech Re: Housing, Correspondence), Nov 1999 (Box 60)
    - Vassar Club of Washington, (Speech, Background Material), 23 Feb 1999 (Box 60)
    - Veterans of the Cold War, Binghamton, NY, (Press Releases, Talking Points), Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 60)
    - Central Islip U.S. Courthouse and Federal Building Dedication Program, 16 Oct 2000 (Box 60)
    - Chicago Mtg. With Mayor Richard Daley, Chicago Housing Authority, (Correspondence, Prep Materials For Mtg.), 11 Jan 2000 (Box 60)
    - Clean Water/Jobs Coalition, (Lazio Testimony, Correspondence), Feb 2000 (Box 60)
    - Columbus Day Parade Program – New York City, (R. Lazio, NY State Dignitary), Oct 2000 (Box 60)
    - Developers Tax Credit Conference, Orlando, FLA, (Correspondence, Itinerary), 1-9 Jan 2000 (Box 60)